黑 鏡
戰火英雄
原創翻譯  雙語字幕
僅供學習 禁止用于任何商業盈利行為
最新最快海外影視字幕下載
翻譯：杏仁斯嘉麗   桃小兔吃冰棒   澈塵
翻譯：靜妹粒   胡說大王   showeryhe
校對：草草
時間軸：倩倩
后期：吉吉  總監：草草
各位  起床了
Okay, my people! Rise and shine.
起床  斯崔普
Get up, Stripe.
你醒了嗎
You awake yet?
-肯定不是在做夢了  -集合
- Sure as shit ain't dreaming no more. - Company!
昨晚何妨村出事了
Something went down last night in Her Falls,
這里以東約三英里處的一個村莊
a village about three miles east.
報告稱  有人闖入食品店  偷了東西
We've got reports of a food store broken into, shit stolen.
當地人認為是蟑螂
Locals think it's roaches.
蟑螂
Roaches!
五分鐘后出發  行動
We head out in five minutes. Let's go!
看來
Hey, so,
你要第一次真槍實彈地打蟑螂了
looks like you're getting your first real-live roach hunt, huh?
新來的
Hey, new!
New!
我叫斯崔普
It's Stripe.
給你個小建議  以防你今天第一次
Here's a little tip just in case you get your first toe-to-toe
跟蟑螂正面沖突
with one of them roaches today.
要是有一只離你這么近
When you see one right here,
別嚇得尿褲子
try not to shit your pants.
那只會激怒他們
It's only gonna piss them off.
-我盡量  -盡量別理列納
- I'll try. - Try to ignore Len.
他準頭可差了  全世界唯一一個
His aim's so bad, he's the only guy on Earth
尿褲子還沒打中的人
who could shit his own pants and miss.
-去你的  村姑  -村姑
- Fuck you, farm girl. - Farm girl?
是啊  狩獵是我與生俱來的本領
Yeah. Hunting's in my blood.
有些人是有天賦的
Some of us are naturals.
出發
Moving out!
好了
Okay.
你現在可以說話了
You can speak now.
肯定是蟑螂
It must have been roaches.
蟑螂  你看見他們了
Roaches, you see them?
看見了嗎
You see?
我沒看見  我聽見了
I didn't see them. I heard them.
這兒一片狼藉
All the mess.
肯定是他們干的
It must have been them.
想吃曲奇嗎
Want a cookie?
-給你  -他們碰了食物
- Here you go. - They've been in the food.
我們得銷毀剩下的一切
We'll have to destroy everything they left.
沒人會吃的
No one will eat it.
我們可以幫你們換一批
We can replace that, okay?
他們毀了制冷機  拆解開  拿走了零件
They destroyed the cooler. Broke it and took the parts.
制冷機  他們偷了制冷機零件
The cooler? They stole parts from the cooler?
他們往哪邊走了
Which way did they go?
土里的腳印往那邊去了
There were footprints in the dirt leading that way.
帕恩·海德科
Parn Heidekker.
海德科  那是姓嗎
Heidekker? Is that a name?
別讓他們來
Stop them coming.
求你了  一定要阻止
Please, you must stop.
好
Okay.
我的孩子很害怕
I have child who is scared.
我會的  我保證
I will. I promise.
斯崔普
Stripe!
我們的朋友認為
Okay. Our friend here thinks that
蟑螂往帕恩·海德科家那邊去了
the roaches went in the direction of Parn Heidekker's place.
他是這兒的信教的怪人
Local oddball, seems to be some kind of religious freak.
安德森  海格
Anderson, Hague,
留在這里  幫他們燒毀食物
I want you to stay here and help them torch the food,
讓他們冷靜  叫他們放心
keep them calm and reassured.
其余人  去拜訪海德科
The rest of you, we're gonna drop in on Heidekker.
問幾個問題  搜查一遍
Ask some questions, sniff around the place.
要是有蟑螂  叫他們知道我們有備而來
If there's roaches, we show we're ready for them.
出發
Let's go.
海德科先生
So Mr. Heidekker
不是社會名流也不是交際型
is not exactly what you call a socialite or a mingler.
似乎有精神問題
Seems like mental health issues.
據說  關于蟑螂  他有些有趣的看法
He's got some interesting views on roaches, by all accounts.
我這就把他的信息加到你們的"麥斯"系統里
I'm putting his info in your Mass system now.
數月前就有人抱怨他
Been complaints lodged against him going months back.
姓名  帕恩·海德科  性別  男
當地人說  他讓蟑螂穿過他的地盤
Locals claim that he let roaches cross his land,
還給他們留下食物
left food out for them.
也可能只是當地村民胡扯  所以...
Could be just shit talk from the local villagers though so...
還剩多少蟑螂
Yo, how many roaches we got left out here?
幾千  還是幾百
A couple of thousand? A couple of hundred, if that?
家鄉那邊有幾百萬呢
I mean, back home we had millions, man.
才兩年時間  他們就又卷土重來
It only took two years to get shit back on track.
這兒還有給他們殘羹剩飯的鄉巴佬
Out here you got rustic fucks throwing them scraps.
難怪消滅他們要那么久
No wonder it's taken so long to mop shit up.
但怎么會有人傻到幫蟑螂呢
But how can anyone be dumb enough to help a fucking roach?
誰說不是呢
Hell, yeah.
前后有門
Portals front and rear.
窗戶被遮住了
Windows blacked out.
煙囪冒煙  有人在家
Chimney smoke. Someone's home.
列納德  用掃描器
Lennard, you use the boomer.
看"麥斯"  都能看見結構圖吧
Okay, Mass check. Everyone got the layout?
-收到  -收到
- Check. - Check.
無人機
收到
Check.
艾金  瓦爾康  科奇  你們去搜查外屋
Aikin, Valcon, Coach, you check the outbuildings here.
每次搜一間  慢慢來
Take them one at a time and slow.
斯崔普  賴曼  你們跟我和列納德一起
Stripe, Raiman, you come with me and Lennard.
我們從這兒進去
We go in here.
列納和我去和海德科談
Len and I will talk to Heidekker,
你們搜查房子的其他地方
you check the rest of the house.
好
Okay.
最理想的結果  不開槍
Optimal outcome, no shots fired.
除了打蟑螂
Except on a roach.
早上好  先生
Morning, sir.
沒必要  我會說你們的語言
There's no need for this. I speak your language.
好
Okay.
-你想干什么  -只想談談
- What is it you want? - Just to talk.
我們不正在談嗎
That's what we're doing.
我們進去談會更親切一點
Be a little more neighbourly if we did it inside.
檢查樓上房間
Check the upstairs rooms.
放松  我不是你的敵人
Relax. I'm not your enemy.
他們在哪
Where are they?
誰在哪
Where are who?
那邊村子里有一群
You know, we got a whole bunch of frightened,
害怕又憤怒的人
angry people in that village.
蟑螂闖進了食品店
Roaches have been breaking into the food stores,
偷了食物
stealing supplies.
你知情嗎
You know anything about that?
不
No.
不光是偷東西的問題
See, it's not just what they stole.
剩下的食品也要被銷毀
All that food left is gonna be destroyed.
-沒人會吃的  -斯崔普
- No one's gonna eat it. - Stripe.
讓每個人都更不好過了
Makes life harder for everyone.
墻上掛著十字架  你有原則
Cross on the wall there. You got principles.
你認為所有生命都是神圣的
Think all life is sacred.
我理解
And I get it.
我同意  所有生命都是神圣的
I agree. All life is sacred so...
所以你連蟑螂也得保護  是嗎
you even got to protect the roaches. Right?
他們那樣不是他們的錯
It's not their fault they're like that.
又不是他們想那樣
They didn't ask for this.
我明白  我們明白
I get it. We get it.
他們血液里有壞東西  才變成那樣的
There's shit in their blood that made them that way.
他們攜帶著疾病
The sickness they're carrying.
疾病才不管生命的神圣
That doesn't care about the sanctity of life
也不管還有誰要受苦受難
or the pain about who else is gonna suffer.
要是在五年  十年  二十年之內
We don't stop the roaches, in five, ten,
消滅不了蟑螂
20 years from now,
還會有孩子生下來就是那樣
you're still gonna get kids born that way,
然后他們還會繁殖
and then they're gonna breed.
找到了
Bingo.
這樣永無休止  痛苦循環往復
And so it goes on. That cycle of pain.
那種病本是可以避免的
That sickness, and it could have been avoided.
該死的蟑螂窩
Fucking roach nest.
你去搜那里  我檢查樓梯
You check in there. I'll take the stairs.
今天你救下的每個蟑螂
Every roach you save today,
天知道
you condemn God knows
明天會有多少人將因此痛苦絕望
how many people to despair and misery tomorrow.
你不能還把他們當人看
You can't still see them as human.
你的情緒我可以理解  但這是錯的
Understandable sentiment, granted, but it's misguided.
人類還想生存下去
We gotta take them out
我們就得把他們鏟除干凈
if humankind is gonna carry on in this world.
事實就是這樣
That's just the hard truth.
必須做出犧牲
Gotta make sacrifices.
搞什么
What the fuck?
幫我一把
Help me out here!
操
Fuck!
*哪怕羞辱我  我也依然在乎你*
*Try to shame me and still I'll care for you*
*隨你東游西逛  就算貶低我[壓倒我]*
*You can run around, even put me down*
*我也依然等著你*
*I'll still be there for you*
小賴
Rai!
拜托  我們回基地得聽一路
Come on. We gotta listen to Mr. Sunday School
主日學校老師念經嗎
all the way back to base?
堵上耳朵就行了
You can cover your ears.
好  或者我按下永久靜音鍵
Yeah, or, uh.... I'll just hit permanent mute.
放下槍
Lower your weapon.
殺蟑螂同情者也算一次擊殺吧
Roach lover counts as a kill too, right?
他是平民
He's a civ, right?
你殺死平民
You shoot a civ,
會終生不得安寧
that's gonna stay with you the rest of your life.
斯崔普
Yo, Stripe,
你可不可以  別那么假正經
why don't you, uh... pull the stick out of your ass?
因為我在作弄他  不是你
Because I'm fucking with him, not you.
看來你倆都信了  是吧
I guess I had you both going, right?
好了
All right!
把這里燒掉
Let's torch the place.
你沒事吧
Hey, you okay, man?
沒事
Yeah.
-我聽說你消滅了一只  -兩只
- I heard you popped one in there. - Two.
慢著  兩只
Wait, two?
我用刀解決了一只
I got another one, with my knife.
用刀  我的天啊
With your knife? Holy shit!
-挺厲害吧  -是啊  你個終結者
- Pretty good, right? - Yeah, you fucking Terminator.
天啊  第一次出外勤  他就殺死了兩只
Damn! First time out, he gets two.
你個走運的王八蛋
You lucky motherfucker, man.
這混蛋要做美夢了
Sweet dreams for this asshole.
今晚你要得到犒賞了
Gonna get a treat tonight.
我愛你
I love you.
神槍手小姐
Miss Sharp Shooter.
看不起人的混蛋
Patronising fuck!
冷酷無情  你是死神
Ruthless! You're the Grim Reaper.
下次不會讓蟑螂跑掉了
Yeah, well, no roach gets away next time.
你還在懊惱那件事
Are you still sweating that?
我從小就追蹤鹿  從不半途而廢
Well, I grew up tracking deer. You never give up.
我討厭被他們逃走的感覺
I don't like it when they get away.
賴曼
總體精準度
真棒
Nice.
如果那畜生跑進了森林里
Yeah, if that fucker made it to the forest,
可能會逃到邊界  徹底消失
probably made it to the border, gone for good.
對你來說沒什么
Yeah. It's all right for you.
你干掉了兩個
You popped two of 'em.
但我很久沒得手了
It's been a while for me.
本姑娘很焦慮啊
You know, the gal is getting twitchy.
得了吧  小賴
Come on, Rai.
你昨晚睡得好嗎
You sleep good?
嗯  還行吧
Yeah, I slept OK.
就只是這樣嗎
What, that's all you're gonna give me?
好吧
Okay?
如果是我一次干掉兩個
You know, if I got two in one go,
我會想來一個小時的高潮
I would want to come for like an hour!
好了  閉嘴
All right, shut up.
好吧
All right.
克尼南格  總體精準度
就是這樣
That's the way.
克尼南格  總體精準度
你沒事吧  伙計
Hey, you okay, man?
沒事  我可能是累了
Yeah, think I'm tired is all.
看來你昨晚的確玩得不錯
All right, so you did have a good night.
39, 40, 41....
42...
43, 44, 45, 46,
47, 48, 49,
50, 51, 52,
53, 54, 55,
56, 57, 58, 59...
堅定且純粹
Strong and pure.
-斯崔普  你沒事吧  -沒事
- Hey, Stripe, you okay? - Yeah.
我也說不清
I mean, I... don't know.
我感覺有點不對勁
I feel a little off.
倒不是病了什么的  只是...
I mean, I ain't sick or nothing. It's just, uh...
去醫務室報道
Report to the sick bay.
進行診斷
Running diagnostic.
你看到了什么
What do you see?
一個立方體
A cube.
-在旋轉嗎  -對
- Rotating? - Yeah.
-現在呢  -一棵樹
- And now? - A tree.
-像是蘋果樹  -碰一下蘋果
- Like an apple tree. - Touch the apples for me.
全中
Full marks.
你是說你頭痛嗎
So you say you had like a headache?
是  不過很短暫
Yeah, but just quick.
不嚴重  只是...
Nothing big, just...
看起來一切正常
Well, everything looks okay.
你的"麥斯"植入物也沒有故障或死機的跡象
No sign of any malfunction or dropout with your Mass implant.
從身體上來說  你的狀態非常好
And physically, you're in exemplary shape.
你剛參加完戰斗  可能會有些副作用
You've just seen combat, you can expect some sort of side effect.
在農舍的時候
There was this, uh... this thing...
有個會發光的東西
with a light on it at the farmhouse.
-蟑螂拿著的  -蟑螂拿著的
- Roach had it. - A roach had it?
-像個手電筒  -手電筒
- Kind of like a flashlight. - Flashlight?
像是
Kinda.
我也不清楚
I don't know.
說真的  你沒事  "麥斯"沒問題
Seriously, you're fine. Your Mass is fine.
血液正常  一切都正常
Blood's fine. It's all fine.
好吧
Okay. Yeah.
或許你該和阿奎特談談
Maybe you should speak to Arquette.
阿奎特是誰
Who's Arquette?
你就是克尼南謝吧
So, you must be Koinanchey?
克尼南格
Koinange.
大家都叫我斯崔普
Folks call me Stripe.
他們為什么這么叫你
Why would they call you that?
應該是也覺得"克尼南格"很難念
Couldn't pronounce Koinange either, I guess.
-真有趣  -謝謝
- That's funny. - Thank you.
稍息  孩子  坐下吧
At ease, son. Sit down.
你最近實現了首次擊殺
So you recently logged your first kills?
兩只蟑螂
Two roaches?
還是第一次出勤  很厲害
First time out. It's impressive.
應該是吧
Yeah, I guess.
發生了什么事
So what happened?
什么  擊殺的事嗎
What, with the kills?
是在一個農舍里
I'm in this, uh... farmhouse.
那里有個密室之類的地方
There's this, like, hidden room or something.
我們進去了  發現他們就在里面
We go in and there they are.
第一個是用槍殺的  一槍斃命
First one, I just... It was automatic. Just pop-pop, you know?
嗯  就像訓練的那樣
Right. Just like in training.
對  就像那樣
Yeah, just like that, yeah. Yeah.
-第二個呢  -他跟我在地上糾纏
- And the second? - I mean, he was on the ground with me.
他
He?
是個男的
It was a he.
所以  是短兵相接了
So, this was close quarters then?
對  他壓在我身上  不斷掙扎
Yeah, he's on top of me. Struggling, I mean...
我夠不到我的步槍  只能刺他
I couldn't reach my rifle so I had to stick him.
刺它  拿刀刺它
Stick it. With my knife.
你對此...感覺如何
And how did that... feel?
-什么感覺  -情感上的
- What, like...? - Emotionally.
沒感覺  一切來得太快  我只是自衛
I didn't. I mean, it was quick. It was self-protection.
我想  我只是覺得松了口氣吧
I guess all I felt was, you know, relief.
只是松了口氣
Just relief?
有其他的感覺也很正常
It's not unusual to experience other feelings too.
甚至是片刻的歡愉
A moment of euphoria even.
應該有吧
Yeah, I guess.
我不知道  我以為也許我會...
I don't know, I thought maybe I'd feel...
我不知道
I don't know.
-有其他感覺嗎  -對  比如...
- Something else? - Yeah, like...
后悔
Regret.
什么的  但我沒有這種感覺
Something like that, but that just wasn't there.
所以再來一次  你還會那么做
So you'd do it again?
當然了
Yeah, sure.
那么  你為什么來這里
So... why are you here?
我不知道
I don't know. I mean...
我感覺不太舒服
I had a few weird moments.
我的"麥斯"好像出了點故障
My Mass looked like it was glitching out.
但你的植入物通過了所有診斷
But your implants, I mean, they passed every diagnostic.
-它沒有問題  -嗯  他們說沒問題
- There is nothing wrong with that? - Yeah, they said it's fine.
我也說不好  我只是...
I don't know, I think I just...
覺得它出了點問題
Felt like something was up with it.
但并沒有問題
But there's not.
是啊
No.
你做了件大事
You did a big thing.
你應該感到自豪
You should be proud of yourself.
好嗎
Okay?
會過去的
It'll pass.
今晚好好睡一覺吧
Let's get you a good sleep tonight, huh?
美美地睡一覺
A real good sleep.
在線審核需要故遮擋敏感部位
原版請登陸 netflix.com
操我
Fuck me.
你真行  笨手笨腳
Way to go, fuck fingers.
看來我們開始審問海德科沒多久
It seems Heidekker didn't stay silent too long
他就招了
once we got to work on him.
他說出了一個據點
He's given up a location,
蟑螂在那里找吃的
someplace the roaches have been scavenging.
那好
Well, all right.
是個住宅區  戰后就一直空置著
It's a housing project that's been empty since the war.
離這里不遠
It's not far from here.
控制處要我們在返回基地前去那兒偵察一番
So control wants us to do recon before we go back to base.
可以快點嗎
Can we hurry it up here?
我們真該把整個森林給燒了  是吧
We ought to burn the whole forest down, huh?
讓那些蟑螂無處可逃
Give those roaches nowhere to run.
好了  看見那個沒
Okay, you see that?
那塊太陽能板看起來比別的幾塊要干凈
Solar panel looks cleaner than the rest.
還有些電纜
And there are some cables.
肯定是蟑螂在偷電
There's got to be roaches leaching power.
為什么是這里
Why here?
天知道
Christ knows.
好了
All right.
我得上報
Better dial it in.
控制處  我是梅迪納
Control. This is Medina.
確認這里有蟑螂
Positive ID.
住宅區處有活動跡象
Signs of activity here at the housing project location.
看到一塊太陽能板
Sighted one solar panel,
似乎最近被清理過  還有一些電纜
looks recently wiped clean and some cabling.
收到
Roger so far.
-你沒事吧  -聞下草的味道
- You all right there? - Smell the grass.
我們通常是什么都聞不到的
We can't usually smell nothing.
-你注意過沒  -沒  從沒注意過那個
- You ever noticed that? - No, I never noticed that.
請示行動方案
Requesting course of action.
沒聽清  請重復一遍
Didn't read. Please repeat.
好的
Okay.
控制處要我們撤退等待信...
Control says we should fall back and await comm--
媽的
Shit!
梅迪納
Medina.
斯崔普  回來  她死了  快
Stripe, get back! She's dead. Come on!
好  準備好了嗎  掩護我
Okay. Ready? Cover me.
小賴  小賴  快
Rai! Rai, come on.
好
Okay.
該死的蟑螂有把步槍  我的老天爺
Oh, fucking roach got a rifle. Jesus Christ.
媽的  人渣
Fuck. Piece of shit.
好了  斯崔普
Okay, Stripe.
第一時間下載無刪減美劇  必須登錄字幕組網站
斯崔普  拜托  振作起來  兄弟
Stripe, come on. Get it together, dude.
他已經開了6槍了
He fired six shots.
他的步槍看起來是老式的  手動槍機步槍
His rifle looks old, bolt action.
再裝填應該需要10秒
Should take him ten seconds to reload.
我們要進去嗎
We go in?
我們進去干掉他  你和我一起嗎
We go in and take him out. Are you with me?
-一起  -我們走
- I'm with you. - Let's go!
跟上我
Follow me!
更好更快的原創翻譯 雙語字幕
準備好了嗎
Ready?
好  三  二  一  掩護我
Okay, three, two, one. Cover me.
來啊  伙計  你搞什么鬼
Come on, man! What the fuck?
這是什么鬼
What the fuck is this shit?
我們走
Let's go.
斯崔普
Stripe!
沒事了
It's okay.
冷靜  冷靜  冷靜
Calm down. Calm down. Calm down.
沒事了  沒事了  我不會傷害你的
It's okay. It's okay. I'm not gonna hurt you.
我不會傷害你的  好嗎
I'm not gonna hurt you. Okay?
走  離開這兒  走
Go on, get out of here. Go on.
這里不安全  有蟑螂
It's not safe. There's roaches here.
走吧  離開這里
Go on. Get.
走啊
Come on!
-賴  你做了什么  -閉嘴  跟上
- Rai, what did you do? - Shut up! Come on!
你做了什么  賴
What did you do, Rai?
找到了
Got ya.
賴
Rai!
不
No!
-快跑  -你到底在做什么
- Run! - What the fuck are you doing?
-你殺了他們  -他們是蟑螂啊
- You're killing them! - They're roaches!
你要殺了他們  賴  去你的
You're fucking killing them, Rai! Fuck you!
你到底怎么回事  你腦袋進水了
What the fuck's wrong with you, man? You got some blown shit.
-清醒點  -不
- Pull it together! - No.
你們還好嗎
Are you all right?
你們得離開這里  快點
You gotta get out of here. Come on.
快啊
Come on!
操
Fuck!
你最好跑快點
You better run.
給
Here.
我不用
I'm all right.
你能看見我真正的樣子
You see me as I am.
我當然能看見你
Of course I see you.
你看不到的不是蟑螂嗎
You don't see roach?
你不是蟑螂
You ain't a roach.
蟑螂都很...
Roaches is all...
不正常嗎
Fucked up?
蟑螂不會說話
Roaches don't speak.
你只是聽不到我們講話
You just can't hear us.
你到底在說什么
What the fuck are you talking about?
你的植入物  你的軍隊植入物
Your implants. Your army implants.
麥斯系統嗎
The Mass system?
他們把它植進你的腦袋里  幫你戰斗
They put it in your head to help you fight,
它會讓你把我們看成另外的樣子
and when it works, you see us as something other.
我們中一個叫盧卡的正在制造一種機器
One of us, Luka, was making a... A machine.
能夠閃光  據說它可以干擾你們的植入物
Light flashes. Said it can interfere with the implant.
你是蟑螂
You're roaches?
但是我見過蟑螂
But I've seen roaches.
我見過他們  他們就像...
I've seen them, they're fucking... like, uh...
-動物  -不  是怪物  我見過他們
- Animals? - No, they're monsters. I've seen them.
那是植入物讓你看到的
The implant made you see this.
操  村民們呢
Fuck. The villagers...
當地人  他們不是軍人
The locals, they... they ain't army.
他們的腦袋里沒有裝麥斯
They got no Mass in their heads.
但他們害怕蟑螂
They're scared of the roaches.
-他們恨那些東西  -所有人都恨我們
- They hate the fucking things. - Everybody hates us.
那他們看到的是什么
Well, what the fuck do they see?
那些平民  他們看到的蟑螂什么樣
The fucking civs, when they look at a roach, what do they see?
就是你現在所看到的
What you see now.
他們照樣恨我們  因為他們一直被這么洗腦
They hate all the same because it's what they've been told.
一切始于十年前
Ten years ago, it began.
戰后
Post-war.
最開始  是篩選  DNA檢查
First, the screening programme, the DNA checks,
接著是登記  執行緊急措施
then the register, the emergency measures.
很快所有人都稱我們是動物  骯臟的動物
And soon everyone calls us creatures. Filthy creatures.
所有媒體  電視  電腦
Every voice. The TV. The computer.
都說我們有病
Say we have... we have sickness in us.
我們的血液有問題
We have weakness. It's in our blood.
他們說我們的血液不能延續下去
They say that our blood cannot go on.
我們不能繼續存活
That we cannot go on.
我的名字原是卡塔里娜
My name was Catarina.
他是亞歷克
He was Alec.
現在我們只是蟑螂
Now we're just roach.
但現在
But now...
現在你看到我了
Now you see me.
賴
Rai?
賴  不
Rai, no!
給我個不殺你的理由
Tell me I shouldn't kill you.
都不是真的  賴
None of it's true, Rai.
你究竟有什么毛病
What the fuck got you?
都不是真的
None of it's true.
見鬼去吧
Fuck you.
起來  靠墻
Get up. Back against the wall.
起來
Get up!
你要我進去嗎
You want me to come in there?
沒事  我可以就這樣跟他談
It's all right. I can just talk to him.
謝謝  布里利
Thank you, Briley.
斯崔普
Stripe.
我們欠你一個道歉
We owe you an apology.
我們沒能發現你麥斯植入物的故障
We didn't spot the fault in your Mass.
我給你拿了杯咖啡
I got you a coffee.
你在農舍中發現的設備
The device you found in the farmhouse,
你跟醫生提起的那個
you mentioned it to the doctor.
是這個嗎
Is this the thing?
我們在你和賴曼搜查的舊街區里也發現了
We found it on an old block that you and Raiman were searching.
貌似他們對我們
Looks like they reverse
無人機上的某些部件做了逆向工程
engineered it from some of our drone parts and so on.
這里的光傳送出一個代碼
The light here transmits a code.
就像病毒  入侵你的麥斯植入物
It's like a virus. It burrows into your Mass,
嘗試從內部將其關閉
trying to shut it down from within.
我跟你說
I tell you,
這些蟑螂比我們想的更有創造力
those roaches are getting more ingenious than we give them credit for.
整件事是個謊言
The whole thing is a lie.
我理解你為什么這么說
I understand why you'd say that, yeah.
蟑螂
Roaches.
他們跟我們長得一樣
They look just like us.
當然了
Of course they do.
這就是他們危險的原因
That's why they're so dangerous.
人類  我們總說自己不好
Humans. You know, we give ourselves a bad rap,
但我們是個真正有同情心的物種
but we're genuinely empathetic as a species.
我們并不真想互相殘殺
I mean, we don't actually really want to kill each other.
這是件好事
Which is a good thing.
但未來需要你消滅敵人時就不是了
Until your future depends on wiping out the enemy.
過來  坐下
Come on, sit down.
我不知道你在學校學了多少歷史知識
I don't know how much history you studied in school.
很多年前  20世紀初
Many years ago, I'm talking early 20th century,
大部分士兵甚至沒開過槍
most soldiers didn't even fire their weapons.
或者就算開槍
Or if they did,
他們也只是朝敵人的頭上放空槍
they would just aim over the heads of the enemies.
他們故意這么做
They did it on purpose.
第一次世界大戰中的英國軍隊
British Army. World War I.
陸軍準將會拿著棍子走在戰隊中
The brigadier, he'd walk the line with a stick
他會抽打他的士兵讓他們開槍
and he'd whack his men in order to get them to shoot.
即便在第二次世界大戰中  交火時
Even in World War II, in a firefight,
只有15%到20%的人會開槍
only 15%, 20% of the men would pull the trigger.
世界的命運懸于一線
The fate of the world at stake
只有15%的人開槍
and only 15% of them fired.
這告訴你什么
Now what does that tell you?
這告訴我
It tells me
戰爭本可結束得更快
that that war would have been over a whole lot quicker
如果當時軍隊能更高效一些的話
had the military got its shit together.
所以我們進行了改進
So we adapted.
更有效的訓練  更好的調整
Better training. Better conditioning.
之后爆發了越南戰爭
Then comes the Vietnam War,
開火百分比上升到了85%
and the shooting percentage goes up to 85.
槍林彈雨  但擊殺率仍然很低
Lot of bullets flying. The kills were still low.
而且真殺了人的軍人
Plus the guys who did get a kill,
大多數回來后出現了心理問題
well, most of them came back all messed up in the head.
直到"麥斯"誕生  才出現轉機
And that's pretty much how things stayed until Mass came along.
"麥斯"
You see, Mass...
是終極軍事武器
Well, that's the ultimate military weapon.
為你提供情報
It helps you with your intel.
瞄準目標  進行通訊  調整心態
Your targeting. Your comms . Your conditioning.
如果瞄準的是妖怪
It's a lot easier to pull the trigger
開槍就容易得多了  對吧
when you're aiming at the bogeyman, hmm?
不僅是視覺
It's not just your eyes, though.
還掌控了你其他的感官
Takes care of your other senses, too.
你聽不到尖叫聲
You don't hear the shrieks.
聞不到血腥味
You don't smell the blood and the shit.
他們都是人類
They're human beings.
你知道他們的DNA里都有什么嗎
Do you have any idea the amount of shit that's in their DNA?
癌癥高發率
Higher rates of cancer.
肌肉萎縮癥  多發性硬化癥
Muscular dystrophy. MS.
魚鱗癬樣紅皮病  智力低下
SLS. Substandard IQ.
犯罪傾向  性行為異常
Criminal tendencies. Sexual deviances.
都在那里
It's all there.
都是篩選查到的
The screening shows it.
你希望下一代是這樣的嗎
Is that what you want for the next generation?
別因為盡了責而難受
Don't feel bad about doing your job.
那些村民做不到
The villagers won't do it.
國內的民眾做不到
The folks back home won't do it.
他們沒有"麥斯"
They don't have Mass.
是"麥斯"讓你下得了手
Mass lets you do it.
你
You.
你是在保護血統
You're protecting the bloodline.
而這是一種榮耀  我的朋友
And that, my friend, is an honour.
根本沒什么榮耀
There's no honour here.
只是殺戮
It's just killing.
-謊言與殺戮  -沒人騙你
- Lying and killing. - No one lied to you.
你一直都是知道的
You knew all of this. All along.
你在說什么
What are you talking about?
是你同意植入"麥斯"的
You agreed to have your Mass implant put in.
接受設置  每個士兵都一樣
Set up. Every soldier does.
我們不可能就這么植入它  用夢境欺騙你
We can't just embed it and feed you a dream.
你的大腦會排斥的
Your mind would reject it.
你得自愿接受
You have to accept it. Willingly.
你就是這么做的
It's exactly what you did.
你看過條款和條件了嗎
So you see the terms and conditions there?
那好長啊
Yeah, that's like a whole essay, man.
這是什么
What is that?
你的授權視頻
That's your consent video.
六個月前你簽約的時候拍的
From when you signed up six months ago.
基本上就是說你同意植入"麥斯"并激活
Basically, it says you agree to Mass implant activation.
-我沒做過這個  -你做過
- I didn't do this. - Yes, you did.
-就像催眠一樣  -行啊
- Works kind of like hypnosis. -Yeah, all right.
你也將同意  你會不知道
Part of what you're agreeing to is not realising
自己處于了這個狀態
you've been put in this state.
能明白嗎  你不會回憶起這次對話
If you follow me. You won't recall this conversation.
還挺有趣的  老兄
That's kind of funny, man.
關掉
Turn it off.
要確認授權
So for you to register consent...
-關了  -請在那兒按指紋
-Turn it off, man. - I'm gonna need your thumbprint there.
-這兒嗎  -是的  請
- Right here? - Yes, please.
挺好玩
That's dope.
我沒那么做
I didn't do that!
-我不記得了  -正如他說的
- I don't remember that! - Just like the man said.
-我知道你很生氣  -去你媽
- I know you're upset. - Fuck you!
怎么回事
What's happening?
我們控制你看到的東西  斯崔普
We control what you see, Stripe.
-我什么也看不見  -因為我們關掉了
- I can't see nothing. - Because we control it.
讓我的眼睛恢復正常
Give me my fucking eyes back.
我來說說你的選擇吧
Let me lay out your options.
讓我眼睛恢復正常
Give me my fucking eyes back, man!
聽我說說你的選擇
Let me lay out your options!
選項一  同意重置你的"麥斯"
Option one, you agree to have your Mass reset.
這幾天的全部記憶
All the recollections of the past few days,
包括這次對話  都將被抹去
including this conversation, erased.
不可能
No way.
選項二則是關禁閉
Option two's incarceration.
-建議你考慮一下  -去你媽
- I'd advise you to consider. - Fuck you!
"麥斯"是你的朋友
Mass is a friend.
如果沒有它
Without it,
你將記得自己做過的每件事
you will remember everything that you did.
我才不要這個爛玩意
I ain't having this Mass shit.
再也不要了  沒門
No more. No way.
好
Okay.
那么
Well...
或許該讓你見識一下沒有麥斯的生活
Maybe you should see what life would be like without it.
怎么回事
What's happening?
我在哪
Where am I?
海德科農場  三天前
Heidekker's ranch. Three days ago.
我都記錄了  斯崔普
I have it all logged, Stripe.
我們可以展示你做過的任何事
We can feed you everything that you did.
不  不
Hey, no, no, no. No.
求求你  不要開槍
Please! Please don't shoot.
Please! Please! Please don't shoot.
-求求你  求求你  -不  不要
- Please! Please! - No! No!
不  停下
No. Make it stop.
不  求求你
No! Please.
停下
Make it stop!
求求你
Please!
不  不
No! No!
不
No!
滾蛋  停下
Fuck off! Stop it!
不
No!
你將看得見  聞得到
You'll see and smell
感受到一切
and feel it all.
你想這樣嗎
Is this what you want?
獨自關在牢房里  不斷循環這記憶
On a loop? In a cell all alone?
我們可以替你抹去
We can make that go away.
這次談話也是
This conversation goes away too.
所有一切
All of it.
但你得說同意
But you gotta say the word.
只需要說同意  斯崔普
Just say the word, Stripe.
一切就都會抹去
And it all goes away.
只需要說同意
Just say the word.